gamejolt.com 2017-09-02

# Privacy Policy on Game Jolt

_This privacy policy is effective as of June 8, 2016_

**For questions or concerns regarding the use of personal information you submit to us, please contact us at[contact@gamejolt.com](mailto:contact@gamejolt.com).**

Game Jolt (the " **Company** ," " **Game Jolt** ," " **we** ," " **us** ," or " **our** ") is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of users of Game Jolt's website, [gamejolt.com](http://gamejolt.com/), including without limitation, all sub-pages (the " **Site** "), and the Game Jolt desktop client software, mobile application, game API, and widgets (the " **Software** ") (collectively, the " **Service** "). We have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform users of the Service of how we use and protect the information we collect through the Service. By using the Service, you consent to Game Jolt's collection, use, storage, deletion, transfer to the United States, and disclosure of personal information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above and covers our collection, use, and disclosure of information we collect through the Service.

Game Jolt is committed to complying with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles of protecting personal data.

This Privacy Policy answers the following questions:

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * How do we use the information?
  * Will we share your personal information with third parties?
  * What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?
  * What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

### What information do we collect about you?

**What is Personal Information?** "Personal information" means information that can be used to identify and contact you. Our Site may be browsed anonymously, but many areas of the Service may not be. If you do not browse anonymously, the Service may collect personal information from you including your email address, postal address, name, username, gender, password, phone number, location, photograph, social media information, credit card information, bank account information, billing information, social security number, and cookies.

**Information You Provide:** You provide certain personally identifiable information to Game Jolt when choosing to participate in various activities on the Service, such as creating an account, uploading games and other products, posting messages in the comment sections, sending feedback or requesting customer service or support, chat messages, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. Additional information (such as address) may be collected when uploading a game, or making a purchase.

You may choose to disclose information about yourself in the various comment boxes and forums around the Service or in creating user "profiles". Information that you disclose in these areas is public information, and will be accessible to anyone who uses the Service.

If you choose to sell games and products on the Marketplace portion of the Service, we may need to collect your social security number, identification card number, and a password in order to stay in compliance with VAT and to prevent fraud.

Game Jolt's collection of personal information is limited to information relevant to Game Jolt's data processing, tax compliance, and payment processing. We will not collect "sensitive information" without your affirmative consent.

**Other Information We Track:** The Service uses passive tracking technologies to log non-identifiable information such as IP address, browser type and Service usage (for example: what pages are accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs). We may also employ "cookies," web beacons, tracking pixels, or similar technologies that provide additional functionality to the Service and help us analyze Service usage more accurately. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do, some features on our Service (such as logging in) will not function normally.

**"Do Not Track":** The Service uses Stripe for fraud prevention and payment processing. Stripe's anti-fraud services are designed to prevent your credit card and other Personal Information from being used in a fraudulent purchase through the Service. Stripe utilizes several tools to minimize fraud losses and to help us determine if a transaction is fraudulent. These include tools that allow Stripe to auto-reject suspicious transactions and notify businesses of potentially-suspicious charges so that we can make the most informed decision possible as to whether accept a charge. Thus, in an effort to protect you against credit card fraud, the Service does not honor "do not track" signals when you use the Service. Stripe may also track your activity over time and over a network of sites. We encourage you to learn more about Stripe and read their privacy policy on their website at <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>.

**Google Analytics:** Our Service uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being viewed.

**Children's Privacy:** We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13, allow them to create accounts, sign up for newsletters, make purchases, or browse the Service. Game Jolt takes children's privacy seriously and encourages parents to play an active role in their children's online experience at all times. We urge parents to instruct their children never to give out their real names, addresses, or phone numbers, without parental permission, when on-line. If you have any concerns about your child's personal information, please contact us at [contact@gamejolt.com](mailto:contact@gamejolt.com).

### How do we use the information?

We use the Personal Information we collect to provide you the services offered on our Service, whether you are just browsing, or are a customer or a seller of games and other products. We use the information we collect to respond to your requests and provide customer service, let you know about new games and other news from Game Jolt, ask for your input and feedback on what we are doing, provide personalized services and recommendations, let you purchase or sell games and other products, and as may otherwise be described in this Privacy Policy or at the time that we collect information from you.

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally identifiable site usage data to improve the quality and design of the Service and to create new features, promotions, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. We also use this information to serve relevant ads on the Service.

We may also combine the information you submit to us with information we have collected from you in other forms, such as through emails or offline, or with publicly available information or information we obtain from third parties.

**Depersonalizing your information:** We may make your Personal Information non-personally identifiable by either combining it with information about other users (aggregating your Personal Information with information about other users), or by removing characteristics (such as your name or email address) that make the information personally identifiable. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. You grant us a royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable and fully transferable right and license to use your Personal Information in connection with the creation and development of analytical and statistical analysis tools relating to the use of the customer data we collect on the Service (the "Analytical Data"). While we will never sell your Personal Information, we may make any commercial use of the de-personalized Analytical Data, including without limitation, sharing the Analytical Data with third parties.

**Changes to Privacy Policy:** If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect the changes. We will post the updated policy here and may notify you if we think the changes will significantly impact the treatment of information you have already provided.

We will share the Personal Information we collect from you under the following circumstances:

**Protection of rights:** Game Jolt will share personal information if we have a good faith belief that (i) access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or a request by law enforcement or governmental authorities, (ii) such action is necessary to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues associated with the Service, or (iii) such action is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of Game Jolt, its employees, clients, or users of the Service.

**Asset transfers:** If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of Game Jolt's assets or a line of business, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of the Service, could be included in the transferred assets. Should such an event occur, Game Jolt will use reasonable means to notify you through a prominent notice on the Service. By sharing your personal information with Game Jolt, you are giving Game Jolt consent to transfer your personal information to a third party in an asset transfer described here.

**Service Providers:** We may share your personal information with third party vendors or service providers that we engage for the purpose of fulfilling product orders or processing information on our and your behalf, such as Stripe. For example, we may partner with other companies to process payments for the Service. Additionally, we may partner with other companies to process, analyze, and/or store data, including, but not limited to, Analytical Data. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. To the extent applicable, we require these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Otherwise, unless we tell you first (such as at the time we collect information from you), or unless it is part of a specific program or feature in which you have elected to participate, we do not share personally identifiable information that we have collected (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their own commercial or marketing purposes.

**Forums:** You should be aware that, when you disclose information about yourself in Game Jolt's forums, comment boxes, chat, and on your user profile, the information is being made publicly available and may be collected and used by Game Jolt or other third parties. When you disclose any information in on our forums and other publicly-available areas, you do so at your own risk.

**EU Privacy Shield Compliance:** Game Jolt specifies in contracts with third parties that handle the personal data collected by Game Jolt that the personal data "may only be processed for limited and specified purposes consistent with" the purposes laid out in this Privacy Policy. Those third parties agree to provide the same level of protection as the EU Privacy Shield.

**Links and Third Parties:** From time to time we may include on the Service links to other websites as a service to you. The third party sites are operated by companies that are outside of our control. Many of the games and other products available for download and purchase on the Service are controlled by third parties, as well. As such, your activities at those sites will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of these third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.

We sometimes work with third parties to add features to our Service. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit certain pages of our Service, or collect cookies that they have previously placed, along with the URL of the page you visited. We do not control those third parties or their use of data. This privacy policy does not cover those third parties' use of data.

**Third party advertising:** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Service. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### What choices do you have about the collection and use of your Personal Information?

When you provide us with personal information by entering in your username, email addresses, or other personal information into the Service you consent to our collecting, using, and sharing it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Control of Your Information:** Game Jolt allows you to control the way we use personally identifying information that we might obtain. At the time you provide personal information, Game Jolt may give you the option of declining any future offers or information about new products, promotions, or services. In addition, many of the "mailings" Game Jolt may send you, such as newsletters, have procedures within them to cancel the receipt of any future mailings.

You may opt out of any disclosure of personal data to a third party or the use of data for any purpose other than the one for which it was initially collected by emailing us at [contact@gamejolt.com](mailto:contact@gamejolt.com). You must provide us with the email address or username associated with your account and the details of your privacy request.

**Data Retention:** Game Jolt retains the collected data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Thereafter, Game Jolt deletes all aforementioned data in its possession within a reasonable timeframe. Game Jolt does not verify the correctness of personal data.

In some cases, we may not be able to delete your personal information, and will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We take reasonable steps and appropriate measures to protect data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Please note that some data may be retained if necessary to resolve disputes, enforce Game Jolt user agreements, and comply with technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Service.

**Access and How to Correct or Delete Your Data:** Any individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his or her query to the following email address: [contact@gamejolt.com](mailto:contact@gamejolt.com). Please include your email address associated with your account and a detailed description of your data request. We will respond to any request for access within 45 days.

In exceptional circumstances, such as where the privacy of other individuals would be violated, where it may reveal trade secrets, or where the burden of expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, we may restrict such requests for access.

### What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

We use standard and reasonable technological and procedural measures to protect the information you provide. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our users' personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the Service and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. We urge you to protect your password by not sharing it with anyone else, and to take measures to prevent it from unauthorized access or disclosure. For example, select number, letter and special character combinations that would be difficult for a third party (or hacking program) to determine, and do not write it down where someone may see it.

**International Transfers:** Personal information collected on the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Game Jolt or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

### Dispute Resolution

**Governing Law:** This Privacy Policy is governed by, and construed under, the laws of the United States of America and the laws of the State of Pennsylvania, excluding its choice of law provisions.

**Mediation:** If you are a resident of a country outside the European Union, you agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you and Game Jolt will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties. You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for 45 days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in or near Hershey, Pennsylvania with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorneys' fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

**Dispute Resolution for Residents of the European Union:** If you are a resident of the European Union, in the event that you have any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you may report your claim to us at [contact@gamejolt.com](mailto:contact@gamejolt.com). We will respond to your claim within 45 days.

Game Jolt will expeditiously investigate and resolve any privacy complaint from any EU citizen at no additional cost to you.

If you are a resident of the European Union, in the event that you have any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you alternatively may report your claim to the European Union Data Protection Authorities located in your jurisdiction.

If you avail yourself of the above options but are unable to remedy your complaint, then you may file a complaint with the U.S. Department of Commerce at the following URL: <https://www.commerce.gov/privacyshield>

If all of the above avenues have been exhausted, then you may seek binding arbitration governed by the JAMS Streamlined Arbitration Rules & Procedures (the "JAMS Rules"), and will be administered by JAMS, except as modified below. The JAMS Rules and Forms are available online at [http://www.jamsadr.com](http://www.jamsadr.com/). The arbitration will take place in or near Hershey, Pennsylvania. If the claim being arbitrated is less than $10,000, then the party filing the arbitration may choose to have the arbitration conducted by telephone, online, and/or be solely based on written submissions. A hearing will be established according to the AAA Rules for claims in excess of $10,000.

**European Privacy Shield:** Game Jolt complies with the EU Privacy Shield Framework regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Game Jolt has certified that it adheres to Privacy Shield Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit <https://www.commerce.gov/privacyshield>.

### Your Options

If you do not agree with the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, it may be best to limit your level of interaction with our Service, which could include simply not providing us with personal information. While this will limit the services that our Service is able to provide, most of the free games will remain playable. This option may be best for those who do not wish to provide the mandatory information required to set up an account.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [contact@gamejolt.com](mailto:contact@gamejolt.com) or by postal mail at:

Lucent Web Creative, LLC   
ATTN: Privacy Policy   
50 N. Linden Rd. #563   
Hershey, PA 17033   
747-999-5658
